my name is Alex Gonzalez and this is my
$2.3 million car collection and I'm I'm
extremely happy to share with you guys
because it took me a very long time to
get it and com from Dunkin Donuts to
nothing there's a lot that I've achieved
so I want to share my cars with you guys
my favorite features what I don't like
and from top to bottom so let's
go oh and by the way they're like 10 11
cars make sure you watch all the way to
the end all right guys so in today's
video I'm going to be reviewing my $2.3
million car collection so I'm going to
rate them from my favorites to obviously
my least favorite I'm going to talk
about the pros the cons my best
experience my worst experience how much
it cost me and honestly what I really
think about it overall and by the way I
am not going to be listing them in order
that's just boring the Feast of purpose
of the video so it's going to be random
what car is my favorite and my least
favorite but we're going to start off
with my least favorite car which is this
Chevy Camaro SS what is this it's a V6
it's a V6 right well whatever the [__]
this is it is my least favorite car so
we got this car originally to set in the
woods but actually one of the guys on my
team ended up really liking it and then
we just kind of like gave it to him so
this is my least favorite car what we
just do with this car is just burnouts
as you guys can see back over here we
have completely blown out the back
Fender cuz when we do the burnouts the
tire pops and then it just slashes out
the fender uh we lost this gas cap cuz
we were throwing cones at it as we were
doing donuts and you guys might think
this car does Donuts yes why well
because it is a six-speed manual
transmission so we po the [__] out of
the clutch of this thing and it
sometimes doesn't turn on so we always
ride around with jumper cables on it and
honestly it's a cool fun car for the
budget but it's not something that I
would ever drive outside of a warehouse
kind of thing like this where we can
just do like degenerate stuff so this
car is fun but it's like sketchy so the
things that I hate about this car is
going to be the way it drives the
transmission and the steering wheel the
steering wheel on this thing is
ginormous so I hate how big this
steering wheel is I feel like I'm in a
truck and you can see how dirty this
shift knob
[Music]
is all right so this is usually what we
get this car for we don't really give a
[__] about it it is my number 11 on the
list these other ones are going to be a
lot funner oh and by the way the price
of this car was like $1,000 I think I
have no idea so it be my number 11 on
the list I give it an overall 6 out of
10 because it is reliable I can't even
lie and it is fun but honestly it's just
a old car that the quality isn't good
but it's actually funner than some of
these cars on this list and let me get
into it right now next which is my
number three on the list out of my 11
cars is going to be my porse 992 GT3
six-speed pts so pts is paint the sample
cuz this color is pretty much like one
of one you can't get this color even if
you wanted to it's extremely ex rare so
this is obviously a beautiful car
cosmetically on the outside it looks
absolutely beautiful you have some
extremely fat tires in the back this is
what I like to call my second goto drift
car in the whole entire fleet I have
three drift cars in the whole entire
fleet and this is probably the funnest
one if I'm doing donuts or maybe just
like getting out of a corner but if I
really want to like do like four lanes
like how I like to do it this is not the
car for it because since the engine is
the in the back it pushes the car
forward versus like like the other cars
that I have engin in the front it's a
lot easier to drift so probably one of
my favorite features about this car is
going to be the actual rear of it so we
have a beautiful tail light that kind of
just you know goes across beautifully uh
obviously this super ideal Wing yeah I
weigh 200 lb probably 205 you can really
get on this stand on it nothing's going
to happen it'll be just fine this is
actually a six-speed so if we were to
come into the inside we have our
six-speed 992 with the bucket seats
which honestly it's super uncomfortable
I honestly hate getting in and out of
this car it makes it extremely
uncomfortable to get in and out of the
car not ideal but honestly who gives a
[__] We're Young nobody gives a [__] we
obviously have our stock wheels right
now which not a big fan of usually every
single other car in the fleet has
aftermarket rims for some reason I just
kind of stay with this little track look
I like the way it looks and the previous
owner that had it for some reason
painted all of these parts glossy black
so they usually come about like a it's
like a matte black and the previous
owner painted it I thought that it was a
wrap no the guy like actually painted it
so I tried to take it off from the front
bumper and I tried to take it off from
the side skirt and it's paint feel they
I [__] it up we have two cup holders
in this so we have one cup holder right
here which you guys can know is actually
cool and then we have a second cup
holder over here which honestly I
actually never use so we have a GoPro
mounts pretty much everywhere throughout
the car cuz usually you know we go
drifting in this with the majority of
the people and this one I've actually
had it for about like 6 months almost
and when I first originally got it I
paid
$300,000 for this car which at the time
was like the peak of it like the like as
soon as it came out now it's probably
worth anywhere from like 250 240
especially the way I've driven it and I
how I have taken care of it oh another
thing this thing is extremely reliable
it's been asking for a qut of oil for
over a month and we are still red lining
every single day no issue the car will
turn on does not matter what it has been
put through also it's a brand new car so
you can't really you know judge it fully
just yet but what I will tell you is
that this [__] is reliable as [__] this
is not carbon fiber and it's a [__]
wrap they put fake carbon fiber on the
roof and soda as a real one my
windshield is cracked so I was doing
push-ups on it one day just for a video
and I sat on like I stood on it and I
cracked it and then the crack has just
slowly been going across the wind sh
sucks all right next is my number five
on the list is going to be my my
widebody Urus so this is actually the
Fest Urus that I ever own and everybody
in their mother has seen a Urus and
owned the year I'm like you know what
like if I'm going to go buy a years
let's make it different so I found this
1016 widebody years with every single
spec checked out cuz I didn't want to
just get another basic Urus and honestly
I don't want to get a Urus at all but I
had a Rolls-Royce coling in and I was
like super bored of it after like 3
months I'm like you know what I need a
new SUV and then I found this so this is
my new wide body ear that I've had for
about 6 months as well I bought this at
the same time as my twin turbo
Lamborghini performante cuz I actually
bought them at like together cuz they
have the same exact look on them like
they have the same color the same wide
body kit same Wheels same everything
same interior so obviously this car
exterior wise is absolutely beautiful so
the wide body on this car is actually
done very very well I've seen many
different types of wide bodies and they
look kind of like cheap this is like
very firm sturdy we obviously have the
hood as well little bit of a turnoff
it's not forged carbon so it's like a
black hood I thought it was going to be
forged carbon like the lambo which we'll
get to there in a second moving on to
the wheels we have these ginormous
three-piece wheels that give it the
aggressive look without these wheels
this car would not have this crazy look
and you can see how wide they are look
how much of this [__] sticks out like
look at this you have like a whole hand
that sticks out from the car just
because of these wheels alone which
gives it the aggressive look we have a
sunroof which I am never a fan of to
because in Miami it gets super hot and I
never want going to have the sunroof
open no TVs and no middle section so
this is actually a five-seater you know
the more exclusive Urus is they're a
four-seater it does have star lights but
everywhere around it because the sunroof
takes up majority of the space beautiful
red interior with red stitching
throughout the whole entire car
something that I don't like about the
sden ppf is that over time you could see
inside here that it would actually like
turn a little bit dirty because dirt
obviously accumulates into there like
also inside here so you can see how like
inside there dirt actually accumulates
into to the edges of the ppf which takes
away from the little bit of the detail
from it trunk space on this car is
obviously pretty big something that I
really do like about this car is that it
came with a tune and an exhaust so you
can see we have capristo exhaust which
this thing actually sounds [__]
ridiculous for what it is and it's fast
as [__] I don't know how much they tuned
it to or what they did to it but it is
super fast one thing about my cars is
that I don't like like doing the work on
them myself like I really like buying a
car that is built saves me time saves me
money and it saves me like the headache
of having to deal with that [__] as a
whole so over here they threw a little
bit of the Mexican flag onto the car I
don't know why they do this on the lambo
it kind of confuses me sometimes the
cars are Italian you should put an
Italian flag not a Mexican flag so
obviously on the driver side you have
your
basic oh my God it sounds so crazy bro
so obviously in here it's just like a
regular year just like another one you
have all of your standard buttons
throughout the interior you have massage
chairs which which are actually very
cool and I personally love this dual
screen that this has to offer so you can
see the aggression I feel like everybody
knows this already but you can see the
aggression like if we go from Strata
which is like the base model all the way
to like Corsa you can see how the revs
just start coming up a lot more
aggressive you can actually hear it like
rev
up it's cold so it's still warming up
everything looks obviously very standard
you know your dual screen on the ears
this car surpris surprisingly enough
actually drives better on the high end
than the Porsche this car is an absolute
Beast extremely reliable obviously gas
you know you're going to eat up gas cuz
you have v82 turbo engine there's really
nothing else other to say than the Urus
is absolutely beautiful the way this one
looks and they're dogs that you can
literally beat on these things all day
every day they're never going to give
you a problem I from the second I get in
this car I am accelerating it to the end
until I get to my destination the only
thing this car will ask for is for gas
nothing else the only thing I don't like
is the way when you put it in Corsa how
the transmission shifts it's a little
bit more aggressive like it actually
like you know it's almost like it's
launching into the next gear it's a
little bit of a turnoff but aside from
that I have absolutely no complaints the
car is absolutely phenomenal I were to
give it a 9 out of 10 and I paid about
$300,000 when I bought it about 6 months
ago now who knows I'll probably take a
huge out on it next is going to be
another wide body that's in my car list
which is actually one of the most random
cars that I've ever bought in and it's
going to be my widebody Dodge Charger
Scat Pack so this car was originally
actually bought to give away with fan
funded which is a prop firm but for
sports bets so if you don't want to you
know basically bet with your own money
you can use fan funded and then they
will Bank you your own picks so you can
pretty much have risk free when you're
betting and this car was to give away in
that company but it never happened so we
kind of just like forgot about it in my
garage and I hate this car so much
because it rides like ass
hear that
rattle yeah this thing has a couple
bodies for sure so obviously this car is
loud cool but it's definitely not fun
because I thought the driving experience
was going to be a lot better but this
car is a literal boat so the interior of
this car is you have a trucker size
steering wheel or maybe I just got used
to the other sports cars that are
actually smaller and sportier this thing
is a little bit more beat up um in terms
of like the Cosmetics here but obviously
we have very clean interior 392 all over
it actually had a camera in the front so
it can catch its victims that it would
run over I think I've driven this car
two times and I've had it for like 4
months because it was supposed to give
away and I don't like driving the cars
that I personally am going to give away
and it realistically just sits in the
garage and catches dust I'm at the point
now where we either might set it on fire
we might just blow it up or probably
just give it away but I don't see myself
driving this car ever it is uh not even
a fun car to do donuts in like I tried
to drift it and it obviously does drift
and it will get get the job done but
nowhere near like the Porsche and
nowhere near like the M3 that I have
which is actually a lot more useful for
drifting this car is more for it's like
blow it up and make it catch fire
honestly this [__] is slow as [__] my
mayback Sprinter is probably faster than
this piece of [__] honestly like this
thing I you can see the tires like we
obviously smoke them like you can
literally see like some dirt back here
you can see how we do smoke the tires on
this car so we use it for what it is but
aside from Donuts this car is no good no
fun but I just really think it is
extremely it just makes a lot of noise
and it doesn't move in terms of
reliability I've only driven it like two
three times and I know these cars
actually tend to be reliable from what
I've heard don't have a lot of
experience myself but it's gotten the
job done for the two three times that
I've used it and I'll give this car like
an overall five out of 10 and obviously
despite everything that I hate about it
the one thing that I do like is if you
know you're kind of want to drift on a
budget and you also want to have like a
daily car that's what this car would be
perfect for probably like six years ago
before all this you know crazy lifestyle
happened I would have definitely owned
this car but now seeing what others can
do this would definitely not want to be
my go-to so I paid about I think $50,000
for this car I mean like it looks good
from like this angle don't get me wrong
and I like it but I feel like the
Driving Experience like for me if a car
is the Driving Experience is not
good look at this [__] [__] even
making me sneeze bro I can't I can't
deal with this [__] if the Driving
Experience is not good to me it's trash
honestly like the car has to drive good
cuz you are the dri you're drive like
you buy a car cuz you drive it and if
when you drive it it's ass why are you
buying it like it can look cool all
right but if you want to get a show car
this is not a show car so the Driving
Experience really throws it completely
off for me and honestly I'm like super
against like show cars I think show cars
is probably one of the dumbest things
you could ever do like the point of a
car is so you buy it and drive it not so
you just park it and look at it car is
meant to be driven oh another thing if
like if you buy a car and you don't
drive it like a man why did you even buy
it so every single car that has been
here has been driven like a man even the
mayag we tried drifting it the other
night that didn't go as plann we almost
ran into that wall over there you see
the tire marks right there show cars
honestly to me is probably one of the
dumbest things ever cuz you're just I
mean if you're obviously extremely
wealthy you just want to use it as art
in a place to store money cool but for
me that I'm young and I want to actually
be able to enjoy and live it up I think
the best thing that I can possibly do is
actually drive the cars not just look at
them next on the list coming at eighth
place is going to be my mayback Sprinter
so I actually never thought I would buy
one of these things the purchase
actually came extremely random when I
bought the when I bought the Phantom
actually literally the guy was like yo I
want to show you something just in case
if you might want to get it and he gave
me a deal that I couldn't resist and
honestly it's become like one of my
favorite cars to use whenever I don't
feel like driving and it looks super
lowkey whenever I want to ride lowkey so
this is my mayback Sprinter which
honestly all the fun part is
realistically in the back so we have a
beautiful blue interior inside of this
car so you guys can see that this is
pretty much where I spend the majority
of my time which is just chilling back
here and it actually comes with a bunch
of different range of things so we have
two different types of Captain chairs
which obviously like our feet could
pretty much like roll up and completely
be like a an executive couch but mobile
which actually very cool and obviously
whatever happens for this chair the same
thing would happened for this chair we
have two little reclinable chairs right
here which these are actually you know
they can go up and down if you have
luggage or if you actually want to lay
down so I can completely move the chair
forward lay down and this can be like a
whole ass like little you know single
bed we also have a TV so this section
right here
I click this button up the TV does go up
and I have Wi-Fi so I can put YouTube
honestly put whatever I want and we have
pretty much like ambient lighting at
night time so it looks like super super
cool speakers in this thing are [__]
crazy it's like a mini club inside of
this car and we have a phone right there
that you can like call straight into the
driver if you want to do whatever it is
that you want to do you just click it
phones them in the front and they will
fix it we also have trays in here you
know you could want to be working on the
go you could pretty much work on your
laptop I personally love this car but
one of the biggest turn offs for me is
personal is a motion sickness so I get
really easy motion stickness if all the
windows are down on the car which makes
it look super super cool because it's
almost like a night Vibe then I would
get motion sickness of the car driving
too fast so I actually had to drive with
the windows up so if I would actually
clicked this button right here and then
put close you can see how all the
windows actually close to the downside
and it pretty much creates literally
like a cave in this whole entire if you
come in and then we close the door this
whole entire thing is literally about to
go like pitch black right now so these
lights are going to automatically turn
off and we're fully pitch black right
now so if I were to open all the windows
then we would obviously be able to see a
little bit on the outside the only thing
is that these are literal limo tints so
it's like zero and if you would actually
want to be able to see inside you just
turn on these strobe lights and then it
pretty much be on so it is pretty cool
another con about it is the way the AC
is set up so we do have vents throughout
the car everywhere here so we have vents
Here There and on that side over there
as well but the thing is that with the
Miami Heat that you know we get 100°
weather Fahrenheit pretty much every
other day during the summer it's not
enough to keep the car cool so you
literally have to have the TV down so
the AC from the front blast into here
and it kind of creates a okay
temperature but the majority of the
temperature in here is actually really
really hot during the daytime at night
time it could actually be a little bit
more cool but the something that I do
need to upgrade and figure out is how do
I get colder AC I probably need like an
extra unit on the outside so that's a
little bit of a con and a turn off that
during the day in traffic it's going to
be really hot in here cuz the AC is
simply not strong enough compared to the
heat from outside something else that I
don't like which is a little bit of
turnoff honestly I'd probably never use
it is actually a cooler so I expected
for this here to have some type of
cooler system honestly just to say that
I have it I would never use it the
Phantom has a cooler and I've never used
it and I probably will never use it it's
just kind of cool to know that you have
it this car also has a four cylinder so
it never wastes any gas so it's actually
extremely convenient but it is very slow
not that you want to go fast in this but
if there's any point that you want to
hul ass it will not hul ass at all so if
I were to rate the mayback Sprinter
overall I probably give it like a nine
out of 10 the only reason is because I
can't drive it myself so for me to
actually enjoy it it has to get driven
and sometimes like you know I just want
to be driving and it kind of sucks I
can't drive it to enjoy it fully how it
should and then also the AC kind of
sucks right now so I do give it a 9 out
of 10 which is very high and honestly I
love it aside from the AC and the motion
sickness I have absolutely no complaints
and highly recommend this car
cosmetically on the outside I don't know
if this is like a cheap kit or something
but you can kind of see how like the
mayback thing is very very very cheap
it's like almost like peeling off which
is very weird this is actually a wrap so
the car is actually Gray under but I
love how the black looks because it
looks super lowkey you won't even notice
that there's a mayback inside of traffic
and cosmetically I think it looks super
super subtle and I love how it has the
Chrome rins which kind of matches like
the Chrome Aesthetics of the car so
outside of the car I love it coming in
at number seven on my list is going to
be my love and hate relationship with my
twin turbo Lamborghini
performante it's crazy right some of you
guys might think why is this car number
seven well let me explain here right now
this car is beautiful it looks amazing
but it is a I rather I rather I rather
drive that actually I might be lying
this is better but that gives me less
problems this gives me more problems and
if something gives me a problems I don't
like it I hate it so this is my
Lamborghini performante with our Mexican
flag right here on the door I don't know
why they keep doing this but this car as
you can see is a perfect match to the
wide body ears that's why I bought them
both together at the same time cuz they
look absolutely beautiful together we
make our way to the front of the car you
can see how we have a real forged carbon
hood so this is real forged carbon and
it was actually wrapped white to kind of
give it the white detail throughout the
whole entire car you have a beautiful
carbon well forged carbon front bumper
if you were to open the hood right here
you can see how we have no hood why
because we have bags so these bags take
up our whole entire front space which
you can actually hear them right now get
filled up or deflating or whatever it
does make our way over here to this side
you can see how we have the same kit as
we have on the years but as well here so
we have our flares we have our Forge
Carbon on the vehicle on this side as
well and then we also have beautiful
three-piece Wheels which these
three-piece wheels are honestly very
very nice on the car and I actually like
how these look rather if they were
actually be white they match the wide
body yours these three piece wheels are
like this kind of gold color looks very
very good you obviously have the big
brakes makes the car this car actually
breaks faster than it accelerates and
then this is where the problems begin
problems begin where the fun begins as
well and that is with this twin turbo
Lamborghini kit by sheepy this is sheepy
build so this is a sheepy build twin
turbo Lamborghini and it looks
ridiculous right you're riding around in
the highway with this you're [__]
spinning
Flames making the craziest noises but
little do they know that you're not
doing that by choice you're doing that
cuz the car is about to blow the [__] up
this car is fun it is fast but it is not
reliable I guess whoever built it cuz I
bought it built as well and the person
that did the bags and did the the whole
nine something is wrong with it I don't
know if it's the computer I don't know
if it's the ECU you can beat the [__]
out of the car for about 15 minutes and
after 15 minutes the computer gets hot
and it starts tripping out first gear
won't work third gear won't work Fifth
and seventh you only have second and
fourth gear and all you have to do is
turn it off off give it like a minute
turn it back on and then it works
perfectly fine like there's just some
type of electricity problem with it and
tuning which I know it's just a little
detail that it but I hate having the
cars in the shop it just feel like why
do I I have the car if it's at the shop
I like having my cars at my house so
I've honestly left it like that forever
so I barely ever drive it so another
detail I do like about this car is how
they did match the engine cover with
that xar which looks really cool because
the xar if you notice it's the same
exact color as the brake and the engine
cover it is the same exact color as the
gold part of the rim so there's a really
really cool detail and this car honestly
is a very big neck breaker and all the
car enthusiasts love it making our way
into the inside of the car this car is
actually black and I really love it
because it has the Comfort Seats but
since it's like super low because of the
bags it's actually a mission to get in
and out of this car but aside from that
I have no complaints from the inside of
the car it's beautiful we have forged
carbon everywhere like literally you
have forged carbon in every single piece
of the car even on these vents right
here we obviously have our airlift kit
here as well and I have absolutely no
complaints when it comes to this car
inside I love it perfect looks great but
the problem is the way it drives with
the bags and the transmission with the
turbo so the bags this car literally
rides like a cloud it literally be like
floating so the drive is [__] so the
suspension ride of this car is actually
like really really trash even though
this is probably like A5 $220,000
suspension kit with the work put in and
all that obviously like you're right and
you're literally like feel like you're
in a cloud the fastest I've gone is
probably like 150 sketchiest thing in my
life because of the bags also the
transmission and the way it's like you
know Works terrible I hate it because it
just it's messed up it's not reliable
but it does sound ridiculous it's
probably one of the best sounding cars
in the whole entire fleet that I have
and kind of makes up some of the brownie
points but the fact that it's there's
always something wrong with it it just
completely kills the rating for me but
aside from that I have absolutely no
complaints on the car like exterior wise
I think this is one of the nicest
looking hurac cons you can ever get
obviously especially with the twin turbo
kit I always ride around without the
back bumper because it looks extremely
aggressive like why would you want to
have a twin turbo kit and not be able to
show it like you want to show your twin
turbo kit something also that I like a
lot about this car is how thick it looks
like when you look at it from the back
like this literally looks like a [__]
beast you have these super thick tires
in the back with plus the twin turbo
crate like that right there just looks
like an iconic car picture that somebody
would have as their wallpaper and I have
it as a driveway up space that I [__]
hate I'm going to replace it with
something very soon could be a hyper car
could be another superar who knows so
coming in at number four in the list is
going to be my BMW M3 f80 so this is
actually like one of my funnest and like
one of my favorite cars it's actually
like one of the cheapest as well so I
have never been a BMW fan in my whole
entire life I've actually hated BMW I've
been more of a Mercedes guy like I would
much rather have a C63 or at least I
thought a c63s versus is an M3 but then
I was completely wrong after I got this
one so this one is actually very very
nice because this is the M3 competition
Series so we have obviously carbon fiber
throughout the whole entire car
literally we have the full carbon kit uh
do all of them come with this Hood yeah
well we have it as well we have pretty
much the basic standard wheels that the
car comes with and this car is actually
red on the inside which I didn't like I
was not a fan of so I wrapped it the
cheap way and I did not do the door gems
which now I'm thinking of wrapping it
white cuzz like this is real carbon
fiber right you see this is not like the
Porsche this is real carbon fiber you
can see the difference so this car is
honestly one of the craziest drift
machines that mankind has ever created
this thing I can drift fourth year going
80 M hour and I'll be completely to one
side and then I'll go to completely on
the other side on the highway in Mexico
remember in Mexico and I can do it with
five people in the car with the street
wet no issue in the street dry so the
car has a little bit of a tune it has an
exhaust it's not super fast like you
know it just has enough power to drift
with four people in the car going 80 M
an hour which is always fun and it
smokes the [__] out of these tires like
this I probably change the tires on this
like every two weeks cuz it smokes them
so fast coming over to the back of the
car obviously after the beat up Duck wi
the back of it looks actually extremely
nice because we also have the thickness
of it so it has a little bit of a curve
to the back of it right here makes it
look like very thick oh look prime
example of what we do in this car so
we're actually drifting and uh I think
we like just scraped the curb just a
little bit we almost lost the whole tire
we hit a little bit of the fender right
here while we were drifting as well
which messed it up a little bit but
honestly this is just my fun car this is
a car I get to just have fun with the
boys if any guests come and I'll just
take them out in this to have fun
something that I don't like about it and
there a little bit of turnoff is that it
is actually automatic so I hate that
this car is automatic I wish this car
was manual because I feel like it would
have been so much more fun but it's a
lot easier to drift in this car because
it is automatic if the car would to be
manual I feel like it' be a little bit
harder cuz you can actually launch this
car with the what what does it have DCT
right yeah so DCT in it so I don't know
all my terminologies about a car but I
am a professional or semi-professional
Drifter if you have any doubts try me
and I will show you what's up the
interface is obviously very basic it's
an older generation or M3 the new one is
actually very nice obviously if you've
been in an M3 before any BMW you hate
this right here so every single time you
get into the car and you hold on to that
right there you're going to get dirty
from the residue that this is going to
leave every single time and it sucks I
tell the car wash guys to take it out
but it just never goes completely out um
we have the dope seats so we have the
red bucket seats this is like my
degenerate car like this is a car that I
would just use to just tear up the
streets for like 15 20 minutes before
the cops come and then I leave so I paid
for this car I think it was like
$75,000 and now it's obviously not worth
that anymore so this has actually been
one of my lowkey cars and if you've been
following me for like the last two years
you would have never known that I had
this car you would have never known that
I had like you would probably never
known I had like two or three cars on
this Fleet it's because I like keeping
my cars some of my cars low-key and I
have like three four other cars that I
keep very lowkey and I do not plan to
show at any point just because sometimes
I just want to ride it around low key
you know so I paid 7 $5,000 for it and
honestly I give this car a 9.5 out of 10
I have no complaints on this car it is
absolutely reliable transmission is good
drifting is good the Driving Experience
is good so I give it a 9.5 out of 10 the
only thing I don't like is a little like
cosmetic stuff so like the doors like
when you have like the little gluey
stuff that always is like peeling off
and also sometimes like when you put it
into first gear it's DCT like it'll like
jump on you and it'll make you feel like
you don't know how to drive an automatic
car that is like manual it's kind of a
little bit of annoying but aside from
that I have absolutely no complaints
from this car and I absolutely love it
coming in and number six on the list is
going to be my 2024 Tesla cyber truck so
actually fun fact I was the second
person in all of Florida to actually own
a cyber Tru obviously now it's like
super redundant a bunch of people have
it but I've had this for about like 3 to
four months almost I was the first
person in Florida to ever have a cyber
truck after Fel so I know Fel Williams
was the first person to have it I was
the second person so we obviously took
advantage and we're like you know what
it's a perfect moment to promo fan funed
so it was like a viral truck at that
time and f that is viral so we pretty
much took advantage so this truck
actually surprised me more than I
thought R I originally got it that's why
it's coming in at number six one of the
main things that I hate about this cyber
truck is the efficiency of it so
obviously this thing is battery powered
and it sucks because it is not fuel
efficient or battery efficient at all
and I don't have a charging station at
my house so it is a mission for me to
actually have to go and charge
it I mean that is kind of cool like this
car is super futuristic but it does kind
of suck that the battery on this thing
runs out like extremely fast even if you
have it in chill mode you constantly
have to be recharging it and it's very
annoying because you can't determine if
you're going to go long distance short
distance with this thing because it just
burns battery all the time aside from
that this thing is an absolute Beast
it's a tank it's huge the interface in
the car is actually really cool the way
you open the doors really cool very
entertaining on how it does that I
actually like how it looks in the
original color as well but the wrap is
what makes it pretty much very unique so
we have it with the purple on it you
know we could have not done the fan
funded on it but you see perfect example
20% and we've barely driven this thing
by it just being parked it will burn so
much battery because of the cameras
always recording or whatever it's doing
but the inside of it is like every other
Tesla I think the steuding wheel is
smaller this actually the first Tesla
that I ever own and ever driven I've
never driven a Tesla before in my life
and I am not a big fan of the whole
electric thing I only got this because
of the you know awareness and how it was
viral and now that I've had it it's
actually become like one of my favorite
cars it's super easy to drive extremely
user friendly so you have a bunch of
different cool features that you can do
inside of here it's very futuristic and
anything that you want to do you can
pretty much figure it out out right away
it almost makes you feel like you're in
the future this car is a beast it has
has become very efficient so obviously
you guys know how you open the tailgate
click this button right here pretty much
goes up and then you click this button
right here and then the tailgate will
come to the downside so this is actually
supposedly used as a cooler so you can
just come here throw a bunch of stuff in
there and use it as a cooler I've never
used it as a cooler I just use it for
storage supposedly I guess for whatever
that is and everything about it is
pretty self-expand it's a Tesla drives
great it's a beast on the road the only
bad thing about it is that it is not
battery efficient and it will take up a
lot of space in your driveway this has
takes up almost two cars worth of space
in my driveway which [__] sucks so
since we did get this before anybody did
we paid the tax which is about like
$180,000 for this almost like $200,000
plus tax and all stuff so we did pay the
price at the time of getting it which
now probably lost 100 Grand already on
it because of how the way we beat it up
the miles and how the Market's gone down
and this is a mass production vehicle so
this is not a you know numbered vehicle
so that devalues the car even more and
uh I would have rate this car overall an
eight out of 10 the main turnoff is that
it is going to be the size of it it's
[__] huge parking in places is a
little bit tricky even though it does
have the rear steering and then also the
battery life is a huge turn off like it
makes me not want to drive the car ever
simply because I always have to be
thinking I'm like [__] I'm about to run
out out of battery soon or if I leave it
there for too long is it going to burn
too much battery so having to worry
about that constantly is just so
annoying but aside from that the drive
is very very good the speed is very very
good it's really fast for what it is and
brakes they work great so I actually
love it I just wish I had better battery
life oh and it does that did you get
that yeah yeah so it like quacked and
[__] so we have it for whenever we lock
it for it to Quack and we've tried to
drift it and it just doesn't do it we
almost flipped the [__] out of this
coming in at number one on my list is
going to be my
2021 Ferrari 488 Pista so this I've
probably had it for about 3 weeks and it
has very quickly become the number one
car on my list and honestly I'm
extremely surprised by this car because
this is my first Ferrari that I have
ever owned so I've had pretty much every
single Lambo I've had every single type
of McLaren so I've had a 570s I had a
720s I also have a 720s MSO that I just
bought off Steve will do it and this
tops every single one of those cars I am
extremely surprised the way this car
performs the way this car drives the
speed of this car the way it handles and
honestly this is one of the sexiest
looking cars I've actually been
extremely against buying one of these
cars for a very long time because of the
price because I paid $5 like $55,000 for
this car which honestly I hated it the
fact that a Ferrari is worth that much
but after buying it I am totally for it
because I had a Lamborghini s Fe and I
paid half a million dollar for it and I
thought it was worth it because of the
V12 numbered car whatever but this tops
a Lamborghini SV by a milestone this car
is a million times better so obviously
first things first when you come to it
you can see these beautiful front end
how it has like a scoop so kind of the
wind comes in through the front gives it
beautiful down force and it just looks
extremely aggressive and sexy and you
can determine the difference between a
48 regular a GTB and a Pista very very
fast by the simple front end of this car
which looks extremely aggressive and
then also this front end don't take it
for granted it's actually huge so this
is this is actually one of the biggest
frks that all of the cars have in the
collection and it is absolutely
ginormous because it actually dips into
this section in here and you're actually
able to store a lot more than you were
able to think so you can see how the
whole hood is carbon fiber so this car
is extremely lightweight which actually
makes this car faster than the twin
turbo Lamborghini that I have so I've
raced it with with multiple different
drivers multiple different scenarios
roads speeds and this by far is faster
than the twin turbo Lamborghini now yes
my twin turbo Lambo is pretty much tuned
right now to be very low horsepower I'm
probably pushing like 900 like 990 and
uh it's a little bit [__] up with the
transmission this thing is fully stock
and it is bypassing it so if I were to
tune up the lambo put it on corn but if
I tune up this and put it on corn I
still have my money on this all day so
moving on over to the side we have these
beautiful BBS wheels which supposedly
there's like a 2-year wait list to get
these wheels which is honestly crazy to
me I did not know these wheels were like
this this car actually came built like
this as well tell you I like finding
cars that are already perfectly looking
also this color is OEM so this is a
Ferrari Color it is extremely rare and
we do have ppf throughout the whole
entire car to make sure that it gets
well taken care of uh moving on to the
interior of the car so this car has I
think one of the sexiest Interiors even
though it's not extremely shout out it
is extremely almost like a low-key Flex
you have suede throughout the whole
entire car which makes it a very classy
luck it also kind of sucks in the heat
cuz it's like very sticky when you're
hot but I like how you can are able to
do this little detail when the car watch
gu is able to put the detail on it
there's carbon fiber everywhere inside
of this car literally carbon fiber on
the dash carbon fiber here something
else that's super cool about this car is
that it has no carpet I don't know if
they all come like this but this one has
absolutely no carpet it's like a very
raw feel it's actually a lot better than
having a carpet carpets always move
around and it's honestly whack moving on
to the back of the vehicle which I think
is the second sexiest part what do you
think is better the front of the car or
the back of the car cuz the back of this
car just looks honestly ridiculous the
the way the body kit is set up and how
the wheels stick out and the stripe it's
just for me a perfect and beautiful
combination and I'm happy that I paid
every single Cent for this car I was
contemplating on buying this car for
like two months and then you will also
have the beautiful V8 twin turbo engine
which has a beautiful display and as of
right now you can clearly see that we
are
stock I wouldn't be able to no there's
any modifications anyways making my way
over here to the driver's side we have
same thing no carpet it's a very raw
feel but it's good cuz it doesn't get
moved around something that I do not
like about the Ferrari Pista is going to
be the turning radius so the turning
radius is honestly ass also that little
deeping noise is super annoying at the
beginning always happens when you turn
on the car and turn off the car so the
turning radius on the Ferrari is
literally just one Spin and that's it
like that's it I literally cannot go
anymore so it's very hard to drift this
car and it's very hard to pop u-turns
very hard to just like move the car in a
very close range it sucks because it
only turns one time and I've had
multiple friends tell me that their
Ferraris all of them do this so it's
kind of like a Ferrari thing but it kind
of you know makes up for the experience
how fast the vehicle is and also I love
how when you rev it I I don't know if
this does this come factory with this
right here or no like how the way like
Factory it does come factory well I
think it's dope cuz whenever I rev it
the revs will come up here as
well so has like a wine to it which
sounds absolutely incredible another
thing that I don't like about the car is
that the speaker systems are not the
best so if you would actually want to be
able to listen to good music and have
aftermarket like base this vehicle you
would have to upgrade it because it
doesn't sound good with the stock when
you would at the market base the Porsche
sounds amazing phenomenal this one
doesn't sound that great you can see how
we have carbon fiber throughout the
whole entire door which makes it
actually a very very great look on the
car and honestly it does kind of suck
that you don't have any you know
futuristic technology that it were to be
right here but honestly I feel like this
car doesn't need it I feel like the more
raw Ferrari look on it is a lot better
and when you're driving this car the
last thing that you're think thinking of
is looking at any screen you're more
focused on the experience and how fast
this [__] is something that I did wish
that I got was a spider so I did wish
this was convertible which would make
this car literally I think the best car
that I would ever own but it does suck
that it is not a spider but it does have
a very nice suede roof as well and
honestly if I were to find the spec just
like this spider I would buite in a
heartbeat and I'd probably still keep
this one as well that is how much I
actually like this car and think
remember I was super against buying a
Ferrari for the longest I've had 20 30
different super cars and I've never
bought in a Ferrari and I'm like you
know what I can't go start with a basic
488 if I'm going to go do it I'm going
to go do it to the best of ability that
I can but sizewise range you know I'm 6
69 and I have perfect range inside this
car and I love it and I've always been
super against buying a Ferrari because I
thought it was like an old man's car I
never thought they were going to
actually be fun when you're young like
me you want to buy Lambo McLaren even
Porsche last thing you think is of a
Ferrari but let me tell you I was very
very very wrong so right now this is my
number one car in the list and I don't
know what might top it I probably am
going to get I have three cars next that
are coming up one of them is going to be
a hyper car which is already like in the
works I can go get it right now but I'm
like you know what let's hold it off let
me keep enjoying the fleet right now but
I do have a hyper car literally just one
phone call away it's waiting for me but
I think that car might top this one but
as of right now this is going to be my
number one car for price um fun
sportiness fastness everything about
this car is absolutely incredible I give
it a 9.8 out of 10 the reason I don't
give it a 10 out of 10 is because that
turning radius it is sucks you literally
can't you know do a proper U-turn if you
were to need to you would have to
reverse super annoying and then the
little beeping noise aside from that I
have absolutely no complaints the car is
extremely reliable I beat the [__] out
of it every single time I drive it and
it drifts beautifully coming in at
number nine on the list is my Canon
Maverick turbo RR x3s I think it is so
this is like the actual best Canam you
can get in the market so this is the
biggest the fastest the loudest and the
widest so a lot of these Canam are
actually very narrow and they flip very
easily this is actually extremely wide
so the odds of you flipping are pretty
low and
honestly I [__] hate this thing bro
like this thing there's not one time
that it has not let me down it's let me
down every single time that I go out
either the belt snaps the battery runs
out of battery it [__] gets stuck in
the middle of a puddle this thing is
just ass oh I have a winch for what I
got stuck in the middle of the forest at
like 3 in the afternoon with the blazing
sun and then this thing just decided to
stop working it was honestly this thing
is more of a mission than it is fun to
be truthfully honest at least the way
I've experienced it here in Miami so
something really cool about it obviously
I was able to put you know set and
forget throughout the whole entire car
and then inside here the drive is
actually not the best but this kind of
like normal when it comes to these type
of cars like the drive isn't going to be
like an actual car rid like if it were
to be a big go car it's always all over
the road it is fastest [__] so in this
car I actually have tune and exhaust
this probably hits like 110 M hour and
it is extremely and obnoxiously loud
that you almost can't even talk and the
noise of the exhaust itself will
actually be louder than the speakers so
we literally have speakers like right
here like in your ear so like whoever's
sitting right here they are having a a
tough time determining if they're going
to listen to the music or the exhaust
that this thing is just ridiculously
loud and I regret doing 100% so mine is
actually street legal so I have mirrors
throughout the whole entire car I have
turning signals I have a horn I have
extra lights and I have tail lights and
this makes it actually street legal just
not in the State of Florida because the
guy that I bought it from did all this
[__] to it and pretty much saved me the
time but at the end of day if you're
riding this on the street you're not
stopping you're you're just going to go
what one of my favorite things about it
is if you want to have like an eventful
like fun thing to do with like guests
that you have over your house this is
definitely the go-to thing because it
will definitely break and if you want to
see how these people react to difficult
situations this will put you in a
difficult situation and it will
determine if that person is a winner or
a loser cuz if this [__] breaks and then
they are a little girl about it and then
they don't man up and you know help you
fix it or whatever you know that's not
the person you want to be around but if
you break down in the middle of a forest
with mosquitoes and in the middle of the
sun and the person you're with help
helps you and you know they're all for
it you got a winner so it's also good
cuz you can have fun in it and you can
test the people that you're with if
they're strong people or weak people so
I paid about $50,000 for this when I got
it it's been about almost like eight
months since I've had it and I've
probably used it like 10 times 15 times
and every single time I've taken it out
it's broken but overall I give this
piece of
[__] three out of 10 I I hate it oh I'm
just show you guys how unreliable this
is in every door I have a belt because
these belt belts break like if it were
to be a piece of pencil it literally
just snaps all the time so I have to
ride around with a brand new belt ready
to change at all
times coming to in the list is going to
be my 2020 Rolls-Royce Phantom now I
have had about four rolls-royces in the
past I've had a Rolls-Royce cullinen
I've had a Rolls-Royce Dawn I've had a
Rolls-Royce Ghost and I actually have
another one coming as well and this is
by far my favorite Rolls-Royce and car
in general that's why it's number two in
the list so this is supposed to be
obviously a show for car you're supposed
to get driven in this car in the back of
it cuz obviously the back of it is the
place where you want to be which is
obviously the captain chair if you will
don't mind this little hole in here this
little Keyhole the car is actually
getting wrapped and I told the guys I'm
like yo are you guys done wrapping it
like no like all right I don't give a
[__] give it to me I got to do a video
with it so it's you know having it's
missing some things because the car is
still actively getting wrapped the car
is actually gray on there gray looks
terrible I only bought this car because
of this interior like this interior is
actually beautiful so they don't make
and this is OEM from Ros Roy so if you
look at the roof as well the roof is
actually orange and it has the orange
star lights everywhere throughout the
roof and obviously orange throughout the
whole entire car and the gray is
actually really ugly anything like I'll
pop up a picture right here but I bought
it just because of the Interior because
none of these rolls-royces from
rollsroyce come with a custom interior
like that they come with very basic ones
and the ones that have the aftermarket
upgraded you know interior that they put
them to like these baby blues and these
all like crazy random colors they look
good but the quality of it is never like
an oem Rolls-Royce interior and this is
an oem Rolls-Royce interior so we make
our way to the front we have a beautiful
orange little detail that we did right
here on the Rolls-Royce logo which
pretty much shows that we have orange
interior we did a full Chrome delete on
the car to make it look like a black
badge is not a black badge not going to
lie to you guys and we wrapped it black
which makes it look extremely aggressive
if we make our way to the front of the
car cuz bro this car is [__]
ginormous and I love it we have a
beautiful big steering wheel I hate that
it's not orange so if this steering
wheel would actually be orange this
would probably be the most gangster car
on the face of the earth I love this
orange roof right here because like when
you're taking a video and you see like
the orange roof like you going to like
this like young Vibe like this
motivational vibe the car is actually
out of battery right now so even if I
wanted to turn it on I can't turn it on
because I guess I left it on with the
lights all night or something so I guys
are going to come now and turn it on but
this car is [__] huge you guys can
see how like there's extraordinary
amount of space in here if you were to
be driving the car or not and even if
you're driving the car you're enjoying
the luxuries of the car like look how
many different features this car has to
offer and I personally like driving this
car more than being driven cuz you just
look like a boss you look like a pimp
riding around in this car with staright
the way it feels you feel like good
driving it I don't like getting driven
inside of this car specifically the back
of this car is actually very cool
because we have multiple different
features that not every Rolls-Royce has
one we have an option where we have this
that lifts to the upside so if the car
would have battery I'd be able to show
you but this actually lifts so if you
don't want to have your feet flat you
can actually lift it and it'll make your
feet like this it's a little bit more
comfortable we also have a TV and a desk
inside this this section right here and
we also have obviously our extra control
panels and then rear controlled seats
makes it super comfortable and then we
have a cooler inside this section with
our little Rolls-Royce cups which we
will never use in the world why this
does not have Rolls-Royce branding and I
think it's legal to drink inside this
car because it is a show for a car and
because of how far you actually are from
the steering whe like look how far the
actual hood of this car is like I'm
sitting back here chilling and for you
to actually see how far that hood is it
is actually crazy far how it is from the
point where I am now so love the size of
this car it is absolutely incredible for
it being driven and show for status and
honestly just feeling like a boss
overall and the looks of this car
there's no crazier look like I I can
guarantee you you pull up to a
restaurant and you hop out of this thing
you would get a crazier look if you were
to get out of the Ferrari Pizza people
just look at this and they think Ultra
wealth even though this kind of has the
same price point even a little bit
cheaper than the Pista people just look
at this and they think it's like an
ultimate boss car which it is and that's
why I like it because it just makes you
feel like super powerful status it's
just you feel like a pimp inside this
car at any given point whether you're on
the driver's side back or even being
driven around some things that I do hate
about this car are going to be the stock
wheels that it has on right now so I've
had this car probably for about 3 4
weeks the majority of the time it's
spent inside the shop just getting
worked on because it didn't come how I
wanted to so I just had it in the shop
so I hate the stocks on this car and
there's actually nothing else that I
hate on this car the way it drives
obviously it's Rolls-Royce Phantom
drives absolutely incredible speed it's
a boat it it does have a V12 twin turbo
so it's going to be fast but it's a boat
has 6,000 lbs the way it rides it's a
[__] Cloud you can literally feel
nothing on the road sound system is
incredible the way you feel and look
inside of it is incredible I have
absolutely no complaints of this car
other than those stock wheels but that's
very fixable and with the new wheels
that I'm going to be getting and aside
from that I [__] love it the only
reason why it's not number one is
because the Ferrari the performance and
everything just blows it out the water
so all in all this car probably once I
finish the wheels once I finish the wrap
and obviously other little imperfections
cuz you can see like I wanted this to be
wrapped as well like or smoked out it's
not obviously that's like 100 bucks not
a big deal but like all in with like
Wheels wrap and everything else that I'm
going to put into it I'll probably be in
above the 400,000 on this car probably
almost half a million dollars or like in
that range and honestly I think it'll be
worth it every single Cent this is by
far the most luxurious and most boss car
I have ever purchased and I've been
strategically waiting to buy it CU I
could have obviously bought it a really
long time ago but I didn't want to like
buy it so fast because like what do I
buy after a phantom like there's no
other like bigger Rose rights what do
you have like an extended Phantom which
is the same [__] at the end of the day
so I bought the one that I wanted I
bought it exactly how I wanted and now
I'm going to spec it out exactly how I
want to so if I were to rate this car I
would give it a 10 out of 10 no
complaints one of the most beautiful and
luxurious cars that I have owned and I'm
very happy to have it part of my fleets
just excited to have it done and
obviously have the battery come back
life